Md Shamsad Anam Reeddhy

 $shams ad. an am@gmail.com \cdot https://github.com/shams adan am \\ Dhaka, Bangladesh$

FRORNT-END DEVELOPER

Creative web developer with three years of experience developing, customizing, and optimizing functional, user-friendly, responsive websites. Pay strong attention to details to deliver efficient web solutions, and build new websites from start to finish, focusing to develop a career in web development sector.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML JavaScript WordPress

CSS, Sass Vue, Nuxt Version Ctronlling with Git Bootstrap, Tailwind React, Next Arduino Programming

Chakra UI, DaisyUI Astro Docker

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Appinion BD Limited Jan 2023 - Present

Software Engineer

Turning Figma and Adobe XD designs into optimized, responsive websites with W3 standard codes. Creating fast-performing, SEO-friendly, cross-browser websites, and integrating APIs.

Fiverr AUG 2020 - Present

Front-end Developer and Client Communicatoin

Communicating with international clients and fulfilling their requirements by crafting pixel-perfect, responsive WordPress websites with optimized performance. Specializing in theme customization and page creation using popular page builders like Elementor, WPBakery, and Divi.

JAAGO Foundation AUG 2020 - OCT 2020

Web Developer Intern

During my internship, I demonstrated strong proficiency in web development, where I successfully built an e-commerce site, customized the official website, and optimized a sponsored school's site. My ability to collaborate seamlessly with cross-functional teams showcased both technical prowess and teamwork.

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATION

BSc (Engineering)

Electornics and Communication Enginereing
Hajee Mohammad Danesh Science & Technology University, Dinajpur

Higher Secondary School Certificate

Notre Dame College, Dhaka

Web Development

Learning and Earning Development Project ICT Division, Ministry of Science and Technology Government of Bangladesh